# **Mahyar Gohari**

# Computer Vision Researcher

mahyargohari.com



Mahyar Gohari



m.goharimoghaddam@unibs.it



<u>Mahyargm</u>



(+39) 351 8468289



Brescia, Italy

# **Summary**

Computer vision researcher at the University of Brescia, in the final year of PhD studies with a focus on multimedia forensics. Possessing 2 years of industry experience, adept at bridging academic expertise with practical applications.

#### Education

# University of Brescia / Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.)

November 2021 - November 2024, Brescia, Italy

Ph.D. Candidate in Information Engineering.

My research focuses on multimedia forensics, particularly in the areas of image forgery detection and auto-tune detection using computer vision methods. I've had the opportunity to lead projects in these domains, contributing to advancements in multimedia forensics while deepening my understanding of the field.

# Amirkabir University of Technology / Master of Science (M.S.)

September 2018 - April 2021, Tehran, Iran

Master of Science (M.S.) in Artificial Intelligence and Soft Computing. During my master's studies, I explored tomato detection and classification by their ripeness, employing object detection methods, in greenhouse settings. This research, alongside my coursework, broadened my expertise in computer vision and machine learning programming.

# Amirkabir University of Technology / Bachelor of Science (B.S.)

September 2013 - November 2017, Tehran, Iran

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) in Computer Science.

#### **Skills**

Programming Languages: Python, C/C++, Bash Scripting, LATEX

Tools and Technologies: PyTorch, TensorFlow, OpenCV, Keras, Scikit-learn, Linux, Git, Docker, etc.

Languages: Persian (Native) - English (Advanced proficiency) - Italian (Intermediate)

# **Experience**

# **Arsam Robotics / Computer Vision Engineer**

May 2021 - December 2021, Tehran, Iran

- Responsible for developing a computer vision model using Python and Tensorflow for the "Phygital" game for kids. In this game a mobile phone mounts on the board game, a digital game runs, and the kid interacts/plays with the game by putting the right physical toy on the board.
- Tested, validated, and reformulated models to deliver accurate prediction of outcomes of interest.
- Read scientific articles, conference papers, or other sources of research to identify emerging object detection trends and technologies.

## **Arka / Computer Vision Engineer**

June 2020 - May 2021, Tehran, Iran

- Responsible for developing an object detection model for aerial images taken by drones.
- Delivered oral and written presentations of results of research to management and other end users.
- Read scientific articles, conference papers, or other sources of research to identify emerging object detection trends and technologies.

### Amirkabir University of Technology / Teacher Assistant

September 2019 - July 2020, Tehran, Iran

- Teacher assistant in four different classes for the "Computer Programming in C" course.
- Selected as the best teacher assistant of computer programming in C based on the students' survey.

# **Publications**

- Zanardelli, M., Gohari, M., Benini, S., Adami, N. (2024).
   PINN-based Approach for Robust 3D Light Direction Estimation in Outdoor Images\_Accepted.
- Gohari, M., Bestagini, P., Benini, S., Adami, N. (2024).
   Spectrogram-Based Detection of Auto-Tuned Vocals in Music Recordings Under Review.
- Zanardelli, M., Gohari, M., Benini, S., Adami, N.
   (2023)SynthOutdoor: a synthetic dataset for 3D outdoor light estimation Accepted.
- Gohari, M. (2021). Detection and Localization of Ripe Tomatoes
   Using Machine Vision. Turkish Journal of Computer and
   Mathematics Education (TURCOMAT), 12(13), 7584-7592.

#### References

• References are available upon request.